Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents E
  - Engerrand, Jorge C. (or George C.) (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 29
      - notes for Gamio, 1913 Jan. 31?
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 28; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 May 3; 5p
    - From Boas, 1913 July 9; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 July 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 July 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. # 30
    - also to Cháney, Garciá, Höpfer, Gameo, León, Pruneda, Rerche, Rÿichart, Dobrosehke, Rickarts, Sologuren, 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20?
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 May 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 June 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 July 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 July 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Dec. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 12 and 1912 May 13
    - To Boas, 1912 May 9 1912 May 21
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 18; 4p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 May 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 May 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 May 15
    - To Boas, 1913 May 25; 10 p
    - To Boas, 1913 June 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 June 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 July 11
    - To Boas, 1913 July 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 July 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 23; 4p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 28
    - To Boas, 1914 July 1
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 June 3
    - To Boas, 1917 June 19
    - To Boas, 1917 June 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 June 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 2p
  - Engl, J. (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 8; 2p
  - Englewood Press' Editor (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17; 2p
  - Englisches Seminar der Kgl. Univ. Berlin (Box 25)
    see Brandl, Alvis
  - English, R.B. (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 30
  - Eno, Lawrence R. (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1937 June 18; 1p
  - Enoch Pratt Free Library, Baltimore (Box 25)
    - see Smith, Gretta, 1936 July 21
  - Entomological Society (Box 25)
    - Annals - see Osborn, Herbert
    - Proceedings - see Baker, A.C.
  - Environmental Effects on Motor Habits of Different Nationalities (Box 25)
    - Plan for movie, n.d., filed, 1935 Mar. 6; 5p
      See Gestures
  - Environmental Influences on Motor Habits of Immigrants (Box 25)
    - 1935 Mar. 6, 3p
      See Scenario Draft
  - Epstein, J. (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 29; 2p
  - Erb, F.A. (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. # 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 7; 1p
  - Erb, F.W. (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 23
  - Erbslöh, Rudolf (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 5; 1p
    - see Emergency Soc. for Ger. & Aust. Sci. & Art, 1920 Dec. 31
      (to Speyer, J.)
    - To Boas, E.L., 1904 June 30; 1p
  - Erdeljanoviç, Jovan (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 5; 2p
  - Erdman, H.E. (Box 25)
    - To Palmer, Archie M., 1927 Nov. 1; 1p
  - Erdmann, Prof. Benne (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1881 June 9
    - To Boas, 1881 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1881 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1882 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1882 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 28
  - Erich (Box 25)
    See Schmidt, Erich F.
  - Erkelenz, Anton (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 23 and Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 16; 2p
  - Erlangen, Universitätsbibliothek (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
      see Heiland, Karl
  - Erlich, Mrs. Antonie (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p
  - Erman, W. (Box 25)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 18; 1p
      enc. list of journals
  - Ernst, Alice H. (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 15; 1p
  - Erpi Picture Consultants (Box 25)
    - see Gray, Howard A., 1936 July 6
  - Erskine, John (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 3
  - Erstein, B. (Box 25)
    - From Schwarz, Herman, 1919 Aug. 25
  - Escúela di Engeineros (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 12
  - Espit, Felipe (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 19; 1p
  - Espinosa, A.M. (Box 25)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 June 17
    - From Boas, 1913 July 9
    - From Boas, 1913 July 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 6; 3p
    - From Boas, 1915 May 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 May 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 July 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 5
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 30 & Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 13
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 15
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1921 May 16
    - From Boas, 1921 May 18
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1929 May 6
    - From Boas, 1929 May 15
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1930 May 10
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 May 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 July 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 July 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 20; 5p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 May 9
    - To Boas, 1915 May 30
    - To Boas, 1915 May 31
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 July 14, June 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 30
    - Receipts dating from 1916-17, 1916 Dec. 31?
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 May 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 July 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 3
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1918 June 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 24
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 17; 5p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep 1
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep 24
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 4, Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1924 May 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 12
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1930 May 6
    - To Mrs. De Busk Smith, 1920 Apr. 26
    - To H. De Busk Smith to FB, 1920 Apr. 26
    - From Foulché-Delbosc, R., 1919 Mar. 10; 2p
    - To Mason, J.A., 1915 Mar. 21
    - To Mason, J.A., 1916 Aug. 17; 2p
  - Estabrooks, G.H. (Box 26)
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 17
    - To Hooton, E.A., 1926 Oct. 21
  - Esther (FB' Sec'y?) (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1921 June 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1921 June 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1921 June 24
    - To Boas, 1921 July 11
  - Ethel -- [see Aginsky, Ethel]
  - Ethnological Society (Box 26)
    - see Hale, H., 1887/112
    - see Brinton, D.G., 1887/111
    - see FB to Powell, J.W., 1887/103
    - see Brinton, D.G., 1887/105
    - see Schurz, Carl, 1887/116a
    - see Powell, J.W., 1887/118
    - see Sturgis, A., 1887/121a
    - see Munn, E.C., 1887/123
    - see Cotheal, A.J., 1887/113a
    - see Cotheal, A.J., 1887/103b
  - Eucken, Rudolf (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 July 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 4; 4p
  - Eucken-Haus, Rudolf Eugenics, 1931 Dec. 31 (Box 26)
    - enc. letter, Savelle, I.K. to FB, 1937 June 22
  - European Serials (Box 26)
    - printed notice, 1920 Apr.; 1p
  - European Students Relief of Am. Relief Admin. (Box 26)
    see Hoover, Herbert C.
  - Evans, C. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 18
  - Evans, Eve (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 11
  - Evans, G.W., -- Dept. of Interior (Box 26)
    - To Boas, 1903 May 25
  - Evans, Luther H. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19
  - Evans, R.P. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 27
  - Evans, Thomas Horace (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1932 June 7
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 28
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 20; 6p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 3
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 24
  - Eveland, A.J. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 13
  - Evermann, Barton W. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 6
  - Evers, F.E. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 14
  - Everybody's Magazine, Editor (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1916 June 22
  - Ewald, L.A. (Box 26)
    - To Boas, 1933 May 27; 2p
  - Excelsior Printing Co. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 20
    - To Boas per J.A. Thomas, 1919 Sep. 25
  - Executive Committee of? (Box 26)
    - To Boas, Order of Business, 1917 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Exiled Writers Committee (Box 26)
    - 1941 From Boas, 1941 Feb. 13
    - 1941 From Boas, 1941 Feb. 20
  - Existenzminimum, Das (Box 26)
    - 1937 Dec. 31
  - Explanatory note [re genealogy], 1935 Feb. 28; 2p (Box 26)
  - Eyre, Edward (Box 26)
    - From Bandelier, A.F., 1907 Jan. 26
  - Eyres, L. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 30
  - Eytel, Carl (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 21; 2p
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents F
  - F., E. (Box 26)
    - To Boas, 1926 July 2; 1p.
      (Heading: Anatomisches Institut. Freiburg)
  - F., M.T. (Box 26)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 3; 1p.
      (Enc: Draft of a paper)
  - Faber, A. Dilworth (Box 26)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 30; 1p.
  - Fackenthal, F.D. (Box 26)
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1918 July 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 July 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 21and Nov. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 July 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 May 30
    - To Boas, 1910 July 2
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 May 17
    - To Boas, 1913 May 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1914 May 25
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1915 May 14
    - To Boas, 1915 May 14
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, ? June 8
    - To Boas, 1916 July 5
    - To Boas, 1916 July 14
    - To Boas, 1916 July 24
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 24
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 16; 1p.
    - (Attached to Boas, F. to Butler, N.M.), 1920 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 May 2; 2p.
    - (State of budget for the dept.), 1922 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 July 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 July 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: budget for 1926-1927), 1926 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Columbia Univ. Dept. of Anthropology Budget 1927-1928), 1927 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: Columbia Univ. Dept. of Anthropology Budget 1927-1928), 1927 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - (Enc. Budget Sheet), 1928 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - (Attached: Columbia Univ. Dept. of Anthropology Budget 1929-30), 1929 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 8
      (telegram)
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - (Enc: Fackenthal, F.D. to Lips, J. Oct. 26, 1934), 1936 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 1p.
    - F.D. Fackenthal -- to T.B. Applegat, 1933 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - F.D. Fackenthal -- from T.B. Applegat, 1935 Mar. 26
    - F.D. Fackenthal -- from W.T. Benkes, 1932 Nov. 12
    - F.D. Fackenthal -- to W.T. Benkes
      - (Attached to Benkes, W.T. To Fackenthal, F.D., Nov. 12, 1932)